

# Tshepo Modise

WEB DEVELOPER



+27 73 642 5147



tshepo.modise@umuzi.org

#### PROFILE

I am a web developer with a vast background in Arts and Design. I develop and design web applications that best cater for the client's needs and best suits the user's experience. I am constantly motivated to up-skill myself and to grow professionally. I aim to perform at my very best when presented wit tasks and to establish myself when given the right opportunity.

## EDUCATION

Umuzi Academy | 2018 - Present

NQF Level 5 Certificate in System Development

Central Johannesburg College | 2016 - 2017

Arts and Design N6

## EXPERIENCE

#### SALES REPRESENTATIVE

The BodyShop (FOURWAYS) | Dec 2015 - Jan 2016

## LINE OPERATOR

Pharma Q | Feb 2013 - Apr 2015

#### SALES ASSISTANT

Ster-Kinekor (SOUTHGATE) | Feb 2012 - Jul 2012

### SKILLS











